Guide to the Crawford Theater Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Playbills and Programs, 1663-1989; Series I
  - Subseries D:, 1861-1989; Series I; 192 linear feet (461 boxes) Largest dimension: 12"
    - 1941 Amherst, MA - 1941 New Haven, CT (H) (Box 359)
    - 1941 New Haven, CT (I) - 1941 New York, NY (C) (Box 360)
    - 1941 New York, NY (D-R) (Box 361)
    - 1941 New York, NY (S) - 1941 Westport, CT (Box 362)
    - 1942 Berkeley, CA - 1942 New Haven, CT (Box 363)
    - 1942 New York, NY (A-L) (Box 364)
    - 1942 New York, NY (M) - 1942 Washington, DC (Box 365)
    - 1943 Boston, MA - 1943 New Haven, CT (Box 366)
    - 1943 New York, NY (A-N) (Box 367)
    - 1943 New York, NY (O) - 1943 Washington, DC (Box 368)
    - 1944 Ann Arbor, MI - 1944 New Haven, CT (Box 369)
    - 1944 New York, NY (A-L) (Box 370)
    - 1944 New York, NY (M) - 1944 Trujillo, Dominican Republic (Box 371)
    - 1945 Ann Arbor, MI - 1945 New Haven, CT (N) (Box 372)
    - 1945 New Haven, CT (O) - 1945 New York, NY (C) (Box 373)
    - 1945 New York, NY (D-N) (Box 374)
    - 1945 New York, NY (0) - 1945 Washington, DC (Box 375)
    - 1946 Ann Arbor, MI - 1946 Moscow, USSR (Box 376)
    - 1946 New Haven, CT (Box 377)
    - 1946 New York, NY (A-D) (Box 378)
    - 1946 New York, NY (F-M) (Box 379)
    - 1946 New York, NY (N) - 1946 Youngstown, OH (Box 380)
    - 1947 Ardmore, PA - 1947 New Haven, CT (A) (Box 381)
    - 1947 New Haven, CT (B) - 1947 New York, NY (A) (Box 382)
    - 1947 New York, NY (B- D) (Box 383)
    - 1947 New York, NY (E-Me) (Box 384)
    - 1947 New York, NY (Mi) - 1947 Westport, CT (Box 385)
    - 1948 Annisquam, MA - 1948 New Haven, CT (F) (Box 386)
    - 1948 New Haven, CT (G) - 1948 New York, NY (Ba) (Box 387)
    - 1948 New York, NY (Bo-I) (Box 388)
    - 1948 New York, NY (J-Pi) (Box 389)
    - 1948 New York, NY (P1) - 1948 Westport, CT (Box 390)
    - 1949 Amherst, MA - 1949 New Haven, CT (E) (Box 391)
    - 1949 New Haven, CT (F) - 1949 New York, NY (C) (Box 392)
    - 1949 New York, NY (D-P) (Box 393)
    - 1949 New York, NY (R) - 1949 Westport, CT (Box 394)
    - 1950 Ardmore, PA - 1950 New Haven, CT (C) (Box 395)
    - 1950 New Haven, CT (E) - New York, NY (Ca) (Box 396)
    - 1950 New York, NY (Ce-M) (Box 397)
    - 1950 New York, NY (N) - 1950 Woodstock, NY (Box 398)
    - 1951 Ardmore, PA - 1951 Munich, Germany (Box 399)
    - 1951 New Haven, CT - 1951 New York, NY (B) (Box 400)
    - 1951 New York, NY (C-M) (Box 401)
    - 1951 New York, NY (N) - 1951 Westport, CT (Box 402)
    - 1952 Chicago, IL - 1952 New Haven, CT (G) (Box 403)
    - 1952 New Haven, CT (I) - 1952 New York, NY (F) (Box 404)
    - 1952 New York, NY (G-O) (Box 405)
    - 1952 New York, NY (P) - 1952 Westport, CT (Box 406)
    - 1953 Antioch, OH - 1953 New Haven, CT (D) (Box 407)
    - 1953 New Haven, CT (E) - 1953 New York, NY (D) (Box 408)
    - 1953 New York, NY (E-O) (Box 409)
    - 1953 New York, NY (P) - 1953 Westport, CT (Box 410)
    - 1954 Boothbay, ME - 1954 New Haven, CT (F) (Box 411)
    - 1954 New Haven, CT (G) - 1954 New York, NY (C) (Box 412)
    - 1954 New York, NY (D-P) (Box 413)
    - 1954 New York, NY (Q) - 1954 York, England (Box 414)
    - 1955 Belfast, Ireland - 1955 New Haven, CT (P) (Box 415)
    - 1955 New Haven, CT (Q) - 1955 New York, NY (D) (Box 416)
    - 1955 New York, NY (E-R) (Box 417)
    - 1955 New York, NY (S) - 1955 Westport, CT (Box 418)
    - 1956 Albany, NY - 1956 New Haven, CT (E) (Box 419)
    - 1956 New Haven, CT (G) - 1956 New York, NY (G) (Box 420)
    - 1956 New York, NY (H-P) (Box 421)
    - 1956 New York, NY (R) - 1956 Westport, CT (Box 422)
    - 1957 Boston, MA - 1957 New Haven, CT (T) (Box 423)
    - 1957 New Haven, CT (V) - 1957 New York, NY (H) (Box 424)
    - 1957 New York, NY (I-N) (Box 425)
    - 1957 New York, NY (O-V) (Box 426)
    - 1957 New York, NY (W) - 1957 Westport, CT (Box 427)
    - 1958 Abingdon, VA - 1958 New Haven, CT (R) (Box 428)
    - 1958 New Haven, CT (S) - 1958 New York, NY (G) (Box 429)
    - 1958 New York, NY (H-P) (Box 430)
    - 1958 New York, NY (Q) - Westport, CT (Box 431)
    - 1959 Bahia, Argentina - 1959 New Haven, CT (Box 432)
    - 1959 New York, NY (A-I) (Box 433)
    - 1959 New York, NY (J-S) (Box 434)
    - 1959 New York, NY (T) - 1959 Westport, CT (Box 435)
    - 1960 Bahia, Argentina - 1960 New Haven, CT (C) (Box 436)
    - 1960 New Haven, CT (D) - 1960 New York, NY (B) (Box 437)
    - 1960 New York, NY (C-K) (Box 438)
    - 1960 New York, NY (L-T) (Box 439)
    - 1960 New York, NY (U) - 1960 Westport, CT (Box 440)
    - 1961 Amsterdam, Netherlands - 1961 London, England (L) (Box 441)
    - 1961 London, England (M) - 1961 New York, NY (B) (Box 442)
    - 1961 New York, NY (C-K) (Box 443)
    - 1961 New York, NY (L-R) (Box 444)
    - 1961 New York, NY (S) - 1961 Westport, CT (Box 445)
    - 1962 Boston, MA - 1962 London, England (S) (Box 446)
    - 1962 London, England (T) - 1962 New York, NY (B) (Box 447)
    - 1962 New York, NY (C-H) (Box 448)
    - 1962 New York, NY (I-P) (Box 449)
    - 1962 New York, NY (R) - 1962 Westport, CT (Box 450)
    - 1963 Chicago, IL - 1963 London, England (Box 451)
    - 1963 Munich, Germany - 1963 New York, NY (D) (Box 452)
    - 1963 New York, NY (E-O) (Box 453)
    - 1963 New York, NY (P) - 1963 Westport, CT (Box 454)
    - 1964 Bath, England - 1964 London, England (C) (Box 455)
    - 1964 London, England (D) - 1964 New Haven, CT (F) (Box 456)
    - 1964 New Haven, CT (G) - 1964 New York, NY (Be) (Box 457)
    - 1964 New York, NY (Bi-F) (Box 458)
    - 1964 New York, NY (G-Ma) (Box 459)
    - 1964 New York, NY (Me-Pi) (Box 460)
    - 1964 New York, NY (P1-S) (Box 461)
    - 1964 New York, NY (T) - 1964 Washington, DC (Box 462)
    - 1965 Bayreuth, Germany - 1965 Moscow, USSR (Box 463)
    - 1965 New Haven, CT - 1965 New York, NY (B) (Box 464)
    - 1965 New York, NY (C-K) (Box 465)
    - 1965 New York, NY (L-Ri) (Box 466)
    - 1965 New York, NY (Ro) - 1965 Williamsburg, VA (Box 467)
    - 1966 Berlin, Germany - 1966 London, England (L) (Box 468)
    - 1966 London, England (M) - 1966 New Haven, CT (S) (Box 469)
    - 1966 New Haven, CT (T) - 1966 New York, NY (C) (Box 470)
    - 1966 New York, NY (D-L) (Box 471)
    - 1966 New York, NY (M-S) (Box 472)
    - 1966 New York, NY (T) - Westport, CT (Box 473)
    - 1967 Brighton, England - 1967 Montreux, Switzerland (Box 474)
    - 1967 Munich, Germany - 1967 New York, NY (D) (Box 475)
    - 1967 New York, NY (E-K) (Box 476)
    - 1967 New York, NY (L-R) (Box 477)
    - 1967 New York, NY (S) - 1967 Westport, CT (Box 478)
    - 1968 Bath, England - 1968 London, England (L) (Box 479)
    - 1968 London, England (M) - 1968 New York, NY (A) (Box 480)
    - 1968 New York, NY (B-I) (Box 481)
    - 1968 New York, NY (J-Po) (Box 482)
    - 1968 New York, NY (Pr) - 1968 Wallingford, CT (Box 483)
    - 1969 Chichester, England - 1969 London, England (Box 484)
    - 1969 New Haven, CT - 1969 New York, NY (C) (Box 485)
    - 1969 New York, NY (D-M) (Box 486)
    - 1969 New York, NY (N-T) (Box 487)
    - 1969 New York, NY (W) - 1970 London, England (Box 488)
    - 1970 Madison, CT - 1970 New York, NY (Ch) (Box 489)
    - 1970 New York, NY (Co-N) (Box 490)
    - 1970 New York, NY (O) - 1970 Westport, CT (Box 491)
    - 1971 Amsterdam, Netherlands - 1971 New Haven, CT (R) (Box 492)
    - 1971 New Haven, CT (S) - 1971 New York, NY (M) (Box 493)
    - 1971 New York, NY (N) - 1972 Kalamazoo, MI (Box 494)
    - 1972 Leningrad, USSR - 1972 New Haven, CT (T) (Box 495)
    - 1972 New Haven, CT (W) - 1972 New York, NY (Ma) (Box 496)
    - 1972 New York, NY (Me-P) (Box 497)
    - 1972 New York, NY (R) - 1973 Detroit, MI (Box 498)
    - 1973 Dublin, Ireland - 1973 New Haven, CT (Box 499)
    - 1973 New York, NY (C-Na) (Box 500)
    - 1973 New York, NY (Ne) - 1973 Washington, DC (Box 501)
    - 1974 Burlington, VT - 1974 New Haven, CT (Box 502)
    - 1974 New York, NY (A-Na) (Box 503)
    - 1974 New York, NY (Ne) - 1975 London, England (T) (Box 504)
    - 1975 Manila, Philippines - 1976 Leningrad, USSR (Box 505)
    - 1976 London, England - 1976 New York, NY (Box 506)
    - 1976 Paris, France - 1977 London, England (Box 507)
    - 1977 New Haven, CT - 1977 Williamsburg, VA (Box 508)
    - 1978 Detroit, MI - 1978 Williamsburg, VA (Box 509)
    - 1979 Brezna, Poland - 1980 Detroit, MI (Box 510)
    - 1980 London, England - 1981 Stamford, CT (Box 511)
    - 1982 Ann Arbor, MI - 1984 New Haven, CT (Box 512)
    - 1985 Chatham, MA - 1989 New Haven, CT Undated (Box 513)
    - Undated
      - U.S.
        - Arkansas - Massachusetts (State) (Box 514)
        - Massachusetts (Boston) - New York City, (C) (Box 515)
        - New York City, (D) - Wisconsin (Box 516)
      - Foreign
        - Austria - France (Box 517)
        - Germany - Turkey (Box 518)
      - Unidentified city (Box 518)
    - Dated, unidentified city (Box 518)
    - Program fragments (Box 518)
  - Subseries E:, 11790-1950; Series I; 8.75 linear feet (30 boxes) Largest dimension: 19"
    The playbills and programs within this series are bound in volumes. They are arranged alphabetically by country, city, and theater (if a single theater is represented by the volume) within the broader headings of British Isles and the United States.
    - British Isles
      - England
        - London
          - Royal Coburg, 1824-1825 May (Box 519)
          - Royal Coburg, 1825 April-October (Box 519)
          - Royal Coburg, 1827 April-November (Box 519)
          - Société Helvétique des Sciences Naturelles, 1871 May-July (Box 520)
          - Covent Garden, Haymarket/King's Haymarket, 1808-1809 (Box 521)
          - Covent Garden, 1828-1833 (Box 521)
          - Covent Garden, 1841 (Box 522)
          - Drury Lane, 1827-1830 (Box 523)
          - Drury Lane, 1832-1833 (Box 523)
          - Haymarket, 1860 (Box 524)
          - Olympic/Madame Vestris' Royal Olympic, 1836-1837 (Box 525)
          - St. James's, 1859 October-December 13 (Box 526)
          - St. James's, 1859 December 24-1860 May (Box 526)
        - Newcastle
          - Theatre Royal, 1819-1820, 1823-1825 (Box 527)
        - Oxford
          - New Theatre and others, 1790-1845, undated (Box 528)
        - York
          - Theatre Royal, 1808-1809 (Box 529)
    - United States
      - Boston
        - Globe, 1872-1873 (Box 529)
        - Boston Theatre, 1874-1875 (Box 529)
        - Ireland, Gordon (collector) Volume of programs from Boston area and Springfield, MA; includes indexes, 1898-1899 June (Box 530)
        - Ireland, Gordon (collector) Volume of programs from Boston area, Springfield, MA, New York, NY, and Scotland; includes indexes, 1899 August-1900 June (Box 530)
        - Ireland, Gordon (collector) Volume of programs from Boston area, Springfield, MA area, and Albany, NY; includes indexes, 1900 July-1901 June (Box 530)
        - Handwritten transcriptions of Boston theater playbills, 1838-1839 (Box 531)
        - Miscellaneous Boston theater programs, 1876-1880 March 27, 1880 March 29-1881 March (Box 531)
      - Detroit
        - Programs from Shubert Michigan Theatre, 1921-1922 (Box 532)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1935 October-1936 Jun, 1936 October-1937 April (Box 532)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1937 August-1938 May, 1938 October-1939 May, 1939 October-1940 July (Box 532)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theatre programs (Box 533)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1940 September-1942 July, 1942 September-1943 July (Box 534)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1943 August-1945 June (Box 535)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1945 September-1947 (Box 536)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1947 September-1948 Jun, 1948 August-1949 May (Box 537)
        - Miscellaneous Detroit theater programs, 1949 September-1950 June (Box 538)
      - Hartford
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from parson's Theatre, 1903 (Box 538)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1904 October-1905 May, 1906 August-1907 August (Box 539)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1907 September-1908 July, 1908 September-1909 July (Box 540)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1909 August-1911 January 12 (Box 541)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1911 January 16-July (Box 542)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1911 September-1912 July 1 (Box 543)
        - Billy S. Garvie (collector) Programs from Parson's Theatre, 1912 September-1913 July (Box 544)
      - New Haven
        - Miscellaneous New Haven theater programs, 1869-1904 (Box 545)
      - New York
        - Amphion/ Amphion Academy, 1888 September-1889 May (Box 546)
        - Union Square, 1873 (Box 547)
        - Palmer's, 1891-1892 October 1, 1892 October 3-1893 August (Box 547)
      - Washington, D. C.
        - Playbills from Washington Theatre; includes index, 1831-1832 (Box 548)
      - Miscellaneous U. S.
        - Programs and ticket stubs from New York and New Haven, 1938-1941 (Box 548)
  - Subseries F:, 1872-1923; Series I; .25 linear feet (1 box) Largest dimension: 20"
    The material within this subseries consists of programs printed on fabric (satin and silk) which are arranged alphabetically by country and city within the broader headings of the British Isles, the United States and Other Nations. The items document the celebration of a first night or anniversary of a production or a special performance.
    - British Isles
      - England, 1893, 1903 (Box 549)
    - United States
      - Boston, 1872-1890 (Box 549)
      - Chicago, 1890-1893 (Box 549)
      - New york, 1883-1923 (Box 549)
      - Philadelphia, 1880-1884 (Box 549)
    - Other Nations
      - Czechoslovakia, 1906 (Box 549)
      - Unidentified, 1887, undated (Box 549)
  - Subseries G:, 1913-1974; Series I; 2 linear feet (5 boxes) Largest dimension: 12"
    The film programs within this subseries are arranged alphabetically by title of film. When several film titles appear on a bill, the program is filed according to the feature film title. Several weekly guides to film showings in the New York City area circa 1920 to 1940 are in folders at the end of the alphabetical run in box 554.
    - A-C1 (Box 550)
    - Co-G (Box 551)
    - H-Me (Box 552)
    - Mi-So (Box 553)
    - Sp-Z (Box 554)
- Pictoral Material, 1800-1980; Series II; 45.5 linear feet (68 boxes, 3 folios)
  This series contains pictorial material relating to the theater and performing arts arranged in three sections: Actors and actress, Motion picture stills, and Other materials.
  - Actors and actresses
    - Select
      - Terry, Ellen (Box 235)
      - Bernhardt, Sarah (Box 236)
      - Cornell, Katharine (Box 237)
      - Hull, Josephine (Box 238)
      - Cowl, Jane (Box 239–241)
      - Duse, Eleanor (Box 242)
      - Gilbert and Sullivan (Box 243)
      - Booth, Edwin (Box 244–245)
      - O'Neill, Eugene (Box 246)
      - Irving, Sir Henry (Box 247)
      - Marlowe, Julia (Box 249)
      - Southern, E. H. (Box 248–249)
      - Eliott, Maxine (Box 250)
      - Fiske, Minnie Maddern Davey (Box 250)
      - Hampden, Walter (Box 250)
      - Lenihan, Winifred (Box 250)
      - Adams, Maude (Box 251)
    - Musical comedy
      - A - Z (Box 252)
      - H - Z (Box 253)
    - Actors; general
      - B - K (Box 254)
      - L - Z (Box 255)
    - Miscellanea
      - Dancers - Spanish, Oriental, Circa 1890-1925, undated (Box 256, Folder 1-2)
      - Ballet, Circa 1890-1929, undated (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - Foreign actors, 1899-1915, undated (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Theaters, 1851-1957, undated (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Shakespearean actors, 1862-1969, undated (Box 256, Folder 6-7)
      - Dramatists, 1883-1951, undated (Box 256A, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1906-1935, undated (Box 256A, Folder 2)
      - Motion picture stars, 1913-1958, undated (Box 256A, Folder 3-6)
    - Portraits
      - Men (A-Z) (Box 257)
      - Women (A-Z) (Box 258)
      - Theaters (Box 258)
      - Opera; Ballerinas (Box 259)
    - Actors: large prints
      - A - D; miscellanea (Box 260)
      - E-T (Box 261)
    - Circus stars; Asian actors and actresses (Box 262)
    - Burlesque (Box 263)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 264–265)
    - Crieahaber Collection: actors and actresses (Box 266–268)
  - Motion picture stills
    See also: box 286
    - A - B (Box 269)
    - C - D (Box 270)
    - E - G (Box 271)
    - H - J (Box 272)
    - K - N (Box 273)
    - O - R (Box 274)
    - S (Box 275)
    - S - W (Box 276)
    - Y - Z; miscellaneous (Box 277)
  - Other materials
    - Miscellaneous (Box 278)
    - Cartes-des-visites (Box 279–280, Box 280A)
    - Cabinet photographs (Box 281)
    - Cabinet photographs (Box 281A)
    - Circus stars (Box 282)
    - Lantern slides: theater lectures (Box 283)
      - Indices of lantern slides and related notes, Undated; 1 (Box 283A)
    - Albums
      - Norcross album (Box 284)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 284)
      - Album of photographs and printed ephemera (Box 285)
    - Motion picture stills: miscellaneous and folio (Box 286, Box 286A)
    - Large pictures (Box 286, Box 286B)
    - Framed photographs (Box 287–291)
    - Engravings (Box 292–299, Box 299A)
    - Theater designs (Box 300)
    - Merchandising manuals, promotion portfolios, campaign books (Box 300A)
- Posters, 1850-1980; Series III; 2 linear feet (6 boxes)
  This series contains several hundred posters announcing and advertising theatrical performances and performers. There is no Box 305.
  Conditions Governing Access
  These posters are restricted due to their very fragile condition.
  - Posters, 1850-1980 (Box 301–304)
    Material in boxes 301-304 are restricted due to their very fragile condition.
  - Posters, 1850-1980 (Box 306)
  - Oversize posters (Box 306-F–306E)
    Materials in boxes 306A-306F are restricted due to their very fragile condition.
- Clippings, 1800-1980; Series IV; 168.5 linear feet (132 boxes)
  This series contains newspaper and journal clippings arranged in the following sections:
  Actors and actresses
  Actors: foreign
  Actors: Shakespearean
  Actors: musical comedy
  Actors: motion pictures
  Dancers
  Circus performers
  Dramatists
  Theaters
  Stock companies, autographs, miscellanea
  Critiques
  Miscellanea
  Scrapbooks
  - Actors and actresses
    - Aa - Al (Box 307)
    - Am - Ar (Box 308)
    - As - Ban (Box 309)
    - Bap - Baz (Box 310)
    - Be - Bey (Box 311)
    - Bi - Bot (Box 312)
    - Bou - Bro (Box 313)
    - Bru - Cap (Box 314)
    - Car - Cha (Box 315)
    - Che - Coh (Box 316)
    - Col - Cot (Box 317)
    - Cou - Dam (Box 318)
    - Dan - Dem (Box 319)
    - Den - Dos (Box 320)
    - Dot - Ed (Box 321)
    - Eg - Fau (Box 322)
    - Fau - Foo (Box 323)
    - For - Garg (Box 324)
    - Garl - Gle (Box 325)
    - Glo - Gri (Box 326)
    - Gro - Harp (Box 327)
    - Harr - Hen (Box 328)
    - Hep - Hov (Box 329)
    - How - Jar (Box 330)
    - Jas - Ked (Box 331)
    - Kee - Kl (Box 332)
    - Kn - Lav (Box 333)
    - Law - Leu (Box 334)
    - Lew - Lo (Box 335)
    - Lu - MacM (Box 336)
    - MacN - Maz (Box 337)
    - Me-Mz (Box 338)
    - N - O (Box 339)
    - Pa -Q (Box 340)
    - Ra - Rosna (Box 341)
    - Ross - Si (Box 342)
    - Sk - Sz (Box 343)
    - T - U (Box 344)
    - V - Wen (Box 345)
    - Wes - Z (Box 346)
    - Miscellanea (Box 347)
  - Actors: foreign
    - Country
      - Austria - France (Box 348)
      - France(cont'd) Germany (Box 349)
      - Greece - Turkey (Box 350)
    - Plays
      - A - S (Box 350)
  - Actors: Shakespearean
    - B-G (Box 351)
    - H - N (Box 352)
    - O - Z; Miscellanea (Box 353)
  - Actors: Musical Comedy
    - Mans - My (Box 354)
    - N - Ra (Box 355)
    - Re - So (Box 356)
    - Sp - V (Box 357)
    - W - Z (Box 358)
  - Actors: Motion pictures
    - Mans - N (Box 359)
    - O - Ro (Box 360)
    - Ru - Tl (Box 361)
    - To - Z (Box 362)
  - Dancers
    - Ballet
      - A - Ko (Box 363)
      - Kr - Sp (Box 364)
      - St - Z; Adaggio A - Z; Miscellanea (Box 365)
      - Art - Productions (Box 366)
      - Cinema - Miscellanea (Box 367)
    - Acrobats - Folk (Box 367)
    - Oriental (Box 368)
    - Spanish; Oriental; Barefoot A - E (Box 369)
    - Barefoot F - Z; Chorus girls 1800s (Box 370)
    - Chorus girls 1900-1935 (Box 371)
    - Chorus girls 1936-1940; Night clubs; Minstrels (Box 372)
  - Circus performers (Box 373–374)
  - Dramatists
    - A - C (Box 375)
    - D-Ha (Box 376)
    - He - Ma (Box 377)
    - Me - Sh (Box 378)
    - Si - Z (Box 379)
  - Theaters
    - Africa - England W (Box 380)
    - England Y - Switzerland (Box 381)
    - T - U. S., New York O (Box 382)
    - U. S., New York P - Z; Miscellanea (Box 383)
  - Stock companies; Autographs; Miscellanea (Box 384–385)
    Box numbers 386 to 416 not assigned.
  - Critiques
    - A - Cinema F (Box 417)
    - Cinema G - Company S (Box 418)
    - Company T - Drama, Russian (Box 419)
      Listing continues on the following page.
    - Drama, S - History E (Box 420)
    - History F - Sc (Box 421)
    - Sd - Theater: (country) (Box 422)
    - Theater (type) - Z (Box 423)
  - Miscellanea
    - Production reviews - Shakespeare plays
      - "All's Well" - "Othello" (Box 424)
      - "Pericles" - "Yorkshire Tragedy" (Box 425)
    - Critical studies - Shakespeare plays
      - A - Z Miscellanea (Box 425)
    - Burlesque and dancers (Box 426)
    - Dancers (Box 427)
    - Dancers; Dancers, French (Box 428)
    - Radio and Television performers (Box 429–430)
    - Film reviews, play reviews, puppets (Box 431)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Bastunov, V. I. (subject) Five albums of clippings, programs, and photographs, 1919-1954 (Box 432)
    - Forbes, Mary Elizabeth (subject) Album of photographs, programs, and clippings, 1898-1935 (Box 433)
    - Wilkin, Josephine (collector) Four albums of clippings and programs of performances attended, 1912-1928 (Box 434)
    - Porter, Ruth Alicia (collector) Album of clippings and programs of performances attended, 1902-1924 (Box 434)
    - Neil Burgess (subject) Album of press clippings, 1893-1897 (Box 435)
    - Weiler, Eugene Andrew (collector) Album of press clippings, photographs and tickets regarding U. S. 19th century variety, circus and other performances, Circa 1800 (Box 435)
    - Album of New York City theatrical production programs, 1939 (Box 435)
    - Cornwell, J. S. (collector) Album of magazine clippings of actors and actresses, Circa 1898 (Box 435)
    - Album of Yale University theatrical programs, 1940-1956 (Box 435)
    - Emerson (collector) Album of press clippings and manuscript material of Haverly Minstrels, 1879-1887 (Box 436)
    - Baker, George Pierce (collector) Album of press clippings regarding Madame Celeste in England and other miscellaneous clippings and ephemera, 1838 (Box 436)
    - Emerson (collector) Album of press clippings and playbills of Haverly Minstrels, Circa 1881 (Box 436)
    - French, Stephen B. (collector) Album of press clippings and a few pieces of correspondence regarding U.S. productions, 1900-1904 (Box 436)
    - Album of programs from New York City productions (Plated as gift of Theatre Guild), 1914-1916 (Box 436)
    - Williams, A. C. and Godley, F. A. (collectors) "Album of Theatre Buildings" - clippings of descriptions and pictures of New York City theatres, Circa 1850-1870 (Box 436)
    - Album of miscellaneous clippings of performers, Circa 1890-1920 (Box 436)
    - Brown, James H. and Emerson (collectors) Album of photographs, autographs and playbills, 1870-1890s (Box 436)
    - Album of U.S. and European production programs, 1890-1900s (Box 437)
    - Album of press clippings and cast lists from programs, 1890s-1900s (Box 437)